cupertinotimes.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy - CupertinoTimes

**Privacy Policy: CupertinoTimes.com**

 **The privacy of our visitors is important to us.**

 **At Cupertino Times** , we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. Whenever you visit our website, our web server will recognize who you are, your browser, operating system, IP address.

When you comment on any post you will need to provide the username and email id which will be stored in the database. Your personal information will  **never** be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside CupertinoTimes.

We use third party advertisements on CupertinoTimes.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this and other sites. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We also use InfoLinks who provide Cupertinotimes with “in text” ads and “in tag” ads. 

Data related to Interest-Based Advertising may be collected by these services for the purpose of serving ads that may be of interest to you while on [cupertinotimes.com](http://cupertinotimes.com/). You can opt out of Interest-based Advertising [here](https://cupertinotimes.com/privacy-policy/).

For any further queries or questions, you can contact us [here](mailto:info@cupertinotimes.com).

* * *
